lifeyourway.net 2014-11-21

# Privacy Policy

The privacy of our visitors is extremely important. This Privacy Policy outlines the types of personal information that is received and collected and how it is used.

Your use of this site, in any and all forms, constitutes an acceptance of this Privacy Policy.

**1\. Log Files**

Like many other websites, we use log files which track:

  * Internet Protocol addresses (IP)
  * Types of browser
  * Internet Service Provider (ISP)
  * Date and time stamp
  * Referring and exit pages
  * Number of clicks

None of this information is linked to anything that is personally identifiable, and it is only used to provide a better user experience.

**2\. Cookies**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information ( _not_ including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

My advertising partners include, but are not limited to, Google AdSense, Burst Media and Amazon.com.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks sponsor advertisements and links on Life Your Way that are sent directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or web beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

Life Your Way has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers, and our privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

**3\. Personal Information**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**4\. Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

In compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 18 years old or older.

**5\. External Links**

While Life Your Way is highly selective about which sites we provide links to, we do not control these web sites, nor do we endorse or otherwise accept responsibility for the content or privacy policies of those sites. We encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on third party sites.

**6\. Other**

Users might be asked to subscribe to our newsletter by providing name and email address to receive communication from Life Your Way. We use a secure opt-in subscription system and we reserve the right to contact subscribers with information related to this website and blog. Subscribers may unsubscribe anytime and every email delivered will contain an “Unsubscribe” link.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to [contact us](http://lifeyourway.net/contact).

Last Updated: January 1, 2014
